# **Parbez Mohammad**

As a proactive, supportive individual with exceptional communication skills who is keen, a quick learner and someone who can bring motivational inspiration to your organisation. As a person who has worked to possess an extremely strong work ethic, with a flexible and systematic approach.

36 Albany Close , London, N15 3RG (+44) 7908436182 parbez\_mohammad@hotmail.c o.uk

## **Experience**

London Metropolitan University (October 2018 - April 2019)

Role: Network Engineer (Work Experience)

Key Responsibilities and Duties:

- Designing and implementing typologies
- Upgrading and maximising performance of current networks
- Undertaking capacity management and an audit of IP addressing as well as hosted devices within multiple data centres
- Speaking to customers via email and phone
- Configuring routing and switching equipment
- Providing remote support to on-site engineers and also to end users/customers during installation
- Providing remote and/or on-site troubleshooting

Cyber Care UK (February 2018 - June 2018)

Role: Cyber Security Consultant (Part time Placement, part of my studies)

Key Responsibilities and Duties:

- Assisting Clients with Cyber Security Issues
- Developing and training in the use of Kali Linux
- Assisting workshops designed for the Metropolitan Police and Counsels
- Working In research and development
- Creating learning resources

Retail Experiences (Next - Summer/Winter 2014,

Poundland - Jan 2015-July 2015, Sainsbury - July 2016- May 2019)

Role: Sales Assistant

Key Responsibilities and Duties:

- Assisting customers with purchase
- Stock Replenishment
- Providing a high quality of customer service
- Recovery
- Working on tills

### Qualification

**London Metropolitan University** (2015 – 2019)

Computer Networking and IT Security [2.1]

Sir George Monoux College (2010 – 2013)

Btec Business level 2 [merit] English functional skills [pass]
Btec Level 3 Extended Diploma in Information Technology [D\*DD]

**Park View Academy (2005 – 2010)** 

8 GCSE's (including maths and English) [A - C]

## **Computer Skills**

Basic: Python, Java, Active

Directory.

Intermediate: Command line tools in Windows and Unix (Kali Linux), Networking command tools using CISCO,

LANs and WANs
Advanced: MS Office

#### **Awards**

CISCO CCNA 1 and 2 CEH (pending)

#### **LEISURE**

- Reading books on IT hardware and software
- Researching new products online for PC building
- Repairing computers for family and friends
- Playing video games
- Playing football to socialise with friends in a competitive way and for physical fitness

#### **REFERENCE**

Available upon request